

PROFILE

Want to put your own image in the circle? It is easy! Select the image and do a right mouse click. Select "Fill" from the shortcut menu. Choose Picture... from the list. Navigate your computer to get the appropriate picture. Click okay to insert your selected image.

Once your image has been inserted, select it again. Go to the Picture Tools Format menu. Click on the down arrow below "Crop" and select "Fill" from the list. This will auto adjust your image to crop to the image. You can click and drag your image to place it appropriately.

CONTACT

PHONE:

+234 803 431 4920

WEBSITE:

Website goes here

EMAIL:

chidiebere.chuma@gmail.com

HOBBIES

Playing Table Tennis Watching Football Watching movies Reading

ANTHONY CHUKWUMA

EDUCATION

Roehampton University, United Kingdom

2015 - 2020

Bagged a Post Graduate Diploma in Business Administration

University of Nigeria, Nsukka, Nigeria

1993 - 1999

Graduated with a Second Class (Honors) Degree in Mechanical Engineering

WORK EXPERIENCE

Zenith Bank Plc. Head of Operations

2004-Date

Managed all aspects of branch banking operations including staffing (in conjunction with the bank's Human Resources Department).

Jenida Secondary School, Rukpokwu, Rivers Sate, Nigeria Physics/Science Teacher

2001-2004

Taught Physics, Mathematics and Sciences to Senior Secondary School Classes.

SKILLS

